Finding aid for the Hearst Corporation Los Angeles Examiner photographs, negatives and clippings - oversize portrait and subject files 7000.3
USC Libraries Special Collections
- Oversize Subject Files
  - L
    - Los Angeles -- Streets (Box 316, Folder 7)
    - Los Angeles -- Water and Power Department (Box 317, Folder 8)
  - M, N, O
    - Ma-Mz (Box 317, Folder 9)
    - Malta (Box 317, Folder 10)
    - Manchuria -- Mukden (Box 317, Folder 11)
    - Maps -- California cities -- A-Z -- Except Los Angeles (Box 318, Folder 1)
    - Maps -- California -- Embarcadero district (Box 318, Folder 2)
    - Maps -- California -- Lakewood to Long Beach (Box 318, Folder 3)
    - Maps -- California -- Miscellaneous (Box 318, Folder 4)
    - Maps -- China and Singapore (Box 319, Folder 1)
    - Maps -- Europe (Box 319, Folder 2)
    - Maps -- Germany (Box 319, Folder 3)
    - Maps -- Highways and Freeways (Box 318, Folder 5)
    - Maps -- Foreign -- A to E (Box 318, Folder 6)
    - Maps -- Foreign -- F to I (Box 318, Folder 7)
    - Maps -- Foreign -- J to Z (Box 318, Folder 8)
    - Maps -- Korea -- To July 1950 (Box 319, Folder 4)
    - Maps -- Korea -- August 1950 (Box 319, Folder 5)
    - Maps -- Korea -- September 1950 (Box 319, Folder 6)
    - Maps -- Korea -- October 1950 (Box 319, Folder 7)
    - Maps -- Korea -- November 1950 (Box 319, Folder 8)
    - Maps -- Korea -- December 1950 (Box 319, Folder 9)
    - Maps -- Korea -- 1951-1956 (Box 319, Folder 10)
    - Maps -- Los Angeles -- City (Box 319, Folder 11)
    - Maps -- Los Angeles County (Box 320, Folder 1)
    - Maps -- Los Angeles County -- Flood Control (Box 320, Folder 2)
    - Maps -- Los Angeles County -- Harbors -- Marina Del Rey (Box 320, Folder 3)
    - Maps -- Los Angeles County -- North County Area -- 1961 40 Page Long Range Plan (Box 320, Folder 5)
    - Maps -- Middle East -- And Middle East Countries (Box 320, Folder 6)
    - Maps -- Pacific Area (Box 320, Folder 7)
    - Maps -- Russia (Box 320, Folder 8)
    - Maps -- Southern California -- Miscellaneous (Box 321, Folder 1)
    - Maps -- U.S. (Box 321, Folder 2-3)
    - Maps -- U.S. -- Honolulu Island (Box 321, Folder 4)
    - Maps -- Water -- California (Box 321, Folder 5)
    - Maps -- World (Box 321, Folder 6)
    - March of Dimes (Box 317, Folder 12)
    - Mary's Hour (Box 317, Folder 13)
    - Meat (Box 317, Folder 14-15)
    - Medicine -- Penicillin (Box 322, Folder 1)
    - Memorial Day (Box 322, Folder 2)
    - Memorials (Box 322, Folder 3)
    - Mexico (Box 322, Folder 4)
    - Mexico -- Baja California (Box 322, Folder 5)
    - Mines (Box 322, Folder 6)
    - Missions (Box 322, Folder 7)
    - Mobots -- Miscellaneous (Box 322, Folder 8)
    - Monkeys (Box 322, Folder 9)
    - Motion Pictures -- Academy Awards -- 1950 to 1959 (Box 323, Folder 1)
    - Motion Pictures -- Academy Awards -- 1960 to 1961 (Box 323, Folder 2)
    - Motion Pictures -- Miscellaneous (Box 323, Folder 3)
    - Motorboats (Box 261, Folder 3)
    - Motorboats -- Hearts Regatta -- 1950 to 1952 (Box 323, Folder 4)
    - Motorboats -- Hearst Regatta -- 1953 (Box 321, Folder 7)
    - Mountains -- Miscellaneous (Box 323, Folder 5)
    - Mount Shasta (Box 323, Folder 6)
    - Museums -- Miscellaneous (Box 323, Folder 7)
    - National Guard -- California -- 40th Division (Box 324, Folder 3-5)
    - National Guard -- Miscellaneous (Box 324, Folder 2)
    - Narcotics (Box 324, Folder 1)
    - Navy Day (Box 324, Folder 6)
    - Ne-Ny (Box 324, Folder 7)
    - Nevada -- Las Vegas (Box 324, Folder 8)
    - Newspapers (Box 324, Folder 9)
    - New Years (Box 324, Folder 10)
    - Nisei Week (Box 325, Folder 1)
    - Nudists and Nudism (Box 325, Folder 2)
    - Nurses (Box 325, Folder 3)
    - Norway (Box 325, Folder 4)
    - Nylons (Box 325, Folder 5)
    - Ob-Ow (Box 324, Folder 11-15)
    - Oil (Box 325, Folder 6)
    - Olympics -- 1948 (Box 325, Folder 7)
    - Olympics -- 1952 (Box 325, Folder 8)
    - Olympics -- 1956 (Box 325, Folder 9)
    - Olympics -- 1960 -- Winter (Box 325, Folder 10)
    - Observatories -- Mt. Palomar (Box 326, Folder 1)
    - Organizations (Box 325, Folder 11)
    - Orange -- Shows (Box 327, Folder 1)
  - P, Q, R
    - Pa-Pz (Box 327, Folder 2-7)
    - Paddleboards (Box 328, Folder 1)
    - Pakistan (Box 328, Folder 2)
    - Palestine (Box 327, Folder 8)
    - Palestine -- 1948 (Box 328, Folder 3)
    - Parades (Box 328, Folder 4-7)
    - Photography (Box 328, Folder 8)
    - Pickets (Box 328, Folder 9-15)
    - Picnics (Box 328, Folder 16)
    - Play, Film (Box 329, Folder 1-6)
    - Poland (Box 329, Folder 7)
    - Politics -- Democratic Party -- National Convention -- 1960 (Box 326, Folder 2)
    - Politics -- Democrats -- Convention (Box 329, Folder 8 - 13)
    - Politics -- Republican Convention (Box 326, Folder 3-8)
    - Polo (Box 326, Folder 9)
    - Power lines -- And Plants (Box 326, Folder 10)
    - Prisons (Box 326, Folder 11)
    - Puerto Rico -- Miscellaneous (Box 326, Folder 12)
    - Quadruplets (Box 329, Folder 14)
    - Ra-Rz (Box 330, Folder 1)
    - Racial Discrimination (Box 330, Folder 2)
    - Radar (Box 330, Folder 3)
    - Railroad Crossings (Box 330, Folder 5)
    - Railroads (Box 330, Folder 4)
    - Railroads -- Monorail (Box 330, Folder 6)
    - Railroads -- Snowbound (Box 330, Folder 7)
    - Ranches/Rancho (Box 331, Folder 2)
    - Rationing (Box 331, Folder 3)
    - Real estate (Box 331, Folder 4)
    - Red Cross (Box 331, Folder 5)
    - Refugees (Box 331, Folder 6)
    - Rescues (Box 331, Folder 7)
    - Rescues -- Sea (Box 331, Folder 8)
    - Restaurants (Box 331, Folder 1)
    - Rifle -- Team and Shoots (Box 332, Folder 1)
    - Riots (Box 332, Folder 2-12)
    - Riots -- Race (Box 332, Folder 13)
    - Rivers (Box 332, Folder 14)
    - Robots (Box 332, Folder 15)
    - Rodeo (Box 332, Folder 16)
    - Roller Skating (Box 332, Folder 17)
    - R.O.T.C. (Box 332, Folder 18)
    - Rowing (Box 332, Folder 19)
    - Rubber -- Regular and Synthetic (Box 332, Folder 20)
    - Rubbish (Box 332, Folder 21)
    - Rugby (Box 333, Folder 1)
    - Rumania (Box 333, Folder 2)
    - Rummage sale -- Pasadena (Box 333, Folder 3)
    - Russia -- Army (Box 333, Folder 7)
    - Russia -- Drawings (Box 333, Folder 6)
    - Russia -- Miscellaneous (Box 333, Folder 4-5)
    - Russia -- Moscow (Box 333, Folder 9)
    - Russia -- Navy (Box 333, Folder 8)
    - Russia -- Women (Box 333, Folder 10)
  - S-T
    - Sa-Sl (Box 336, Folder 1-5)
    - Salvage and Scrap Metal (Box 336, Folder 6)
    - Santa Claus (Box 337, Folder 1)
    - Schools (Box 334, Folder 1)
    - Shangri-La (Box 337, Folder 2)
    - Shipbuilding and Shipyards (Box 337, Folder 3)
    - Ships -- Proposed Atom Powered Merchant Ship (Box 335, Folder 14)
    - Ships -- S.S. A-B (Box 341, Folder 1)
    - Ships -- S.S. America (Box 335, Folder 13)
    - Ships -- S.S. American Farmer (Box 335, Folder 7)
    - Ships -- S.S. Andrea Doria -- Italian Liner Sunk (Box 335, Folder 12)
    - Ships -- S.S. Batory (Box 335, Folder 11)
    - Ships -- S.S. C-D (Box 341, Folder 2)
    - Ships -- S.S. E-F (Box 341, Folder 3)
    - Ships -- S.S. Europa (Box 335, Folder 10)
    - Ships -- S.S. Flying Enterprise (Box 335, Folder 9)
    - Ships -- S.S. G-H (Box 341, Folder 4)
    - Ships -- S.S. I-L (Box 341, Folder 5)
    - Ships -- S.S. Iroquois (Box 335, Folder 6)
    - Ships -- S.S. M (Box 341, Folder 6)
    - Ships -- S.S. N (Box 341, Folder 7)
    - Ships -- S.S. Normandie (Box 335, Folder 5)
    - Ships -- S.S. O (Box 341, Folder 8)
    - Ships -- S.S. P-R (Box 341, Folder 9)
    - Ships -- S.S. President Coolidge (Box 335, Folder 4)
    - Ships -- S.S. Queen Elizabeth (Box 335, Folder 3)
    - Ships -- S.S. Queen Mary (Box 335, Folder 2)
    - Ships -- S.S. S (Box 341, Folder 10)
    - Ships -- S.S. Stockholm (Box 335, Folder 8)
    - Ships -- S.S. United States (Box 335, Folder 1)
    - Ships -- S.S. Yukon (Box 335, Folder 15)
    - Ships -- T-Z (Box 335, Folder 16)
    - Sicily (Box 337, Folder 4)
    - Singapore (Box 337, Folder 5)
    - Skiing (Box 337, Folder 6)
    - Sm-Sq (Box 336, Folder 7-9)
    - Snakes (Box 337, Folder 8)
    - Soccer (Box 337, Folder 7)
    - Softball (Box 337, Folder 9)
    - Sororities (Box 337, Folder 10)
    - Space -- Animals (Box 338, Folder 2)
    - Space -- Bases -- Miscellaneous (Box 338, Folder 3)
    - Space -- Miscellaneous (Box 338, Folder 1)
    - Space -- Projects -- Discoverer I (Box 339, Folder 1)
    - Space -- Projects -- Jupiter "C" -- Explorer I (Box 339, Folder 2)
    - Space -- Projects -- Miscellaneous (Box 340, Folder 1-2)
    - Space -- Projects -- Vanguard II -- "Weather Eye" (Box 339, Folder 3)
    - Space -- Rockets (Box 338, Folder 4-8)
    - Space -- Rockets -- A-M -- Miscellaneous (Box 339, Folder 4)
    - Space -- Rockets -- Atlas (Box 340, Folder 3)
    - Space -- Rockets -- German -- V-2 (Box 339, Folder 5)
    - Space -- Rockets -- N-Z -- Miscellaneous (Box 339, Folder 6)
    - Space -- Rockets -- Nike (Box 339, Folder 7)
    - Space -- Rockets -- Regulus (Box 339, Folder 8)
    - Space -- Rockets -- Thor (Box 339, Folder 9)
    - Space -- Rockets -- Vanguard (Box 339, Folder 10)
    - Space -- Satellites -- Miscellaneous (Box 339, Folder 11)
    - Space -- Ship -- X-15 (Box 339, Folder 13)
    - Space -- Ships, Crafts, Vehicles, Capsules -- Miscellaneous (Box 339, Folder 12)
    - Space -- Travel -- Miscellaneous (Box 340, Folder 4-5)
    - Sports Arena (Box 340, Folder 6-7)
    - Sports Arena -- Diagram -- Floor Plan (Box 340, Folder 8)
    - Sports Arena -- Floor Plan -- Los Angeles Memorial Sports Arena (Box 340, Folder 9)
    - St -- Miscellaneous (Box 336, Folder 10)
    - Stadiums -- Chavez Ravine (Box 342, Folder 1)
    - Stadiums -- Coliseum -- Los Angeles (Box 342, Folder 2-4)
    - Stadiums -- Miscellaneous (Box 340, Folder 10)
    - Stadiums -- Wrigley Field -- Los Angeles (Box 340, Folder 11)
    - Statue of Liberty (Box 342, Folder 5)
    - Steel Industry (Box 342, Folder 6)
    - Street Railways -- L.A.T.L. (Box 242, Folder 7)
    - Strikes -- Auto Workers (Box 343, Folder 3)
    - Strikes -- Aviation (Box 343, Folder 4)
    - Strikes -- Coal (Box 344, Folder 1)
    - Strikes -- Foreign (Box 344, Folder 2)
    - Strikes -- General Electric (Box 344, Folder 3)
    - Strikes -- Hawaii (Box 344, Folder 4)
    - Strikes -- Local (Box 344, Folder 5)
    - Strikes -- Longshoremen (Box 344, Folder 6)
    - Strikes -- Maritime (Box 344, Folder 7)
    - Strikes -- Meat Packers (Box 344, Folder 8)
    - Strikes -- Milk (Box 344, Folder 9)
    - Strikes -- Miscellaneous (Box 343, Folder 1-2)
    - Strikes -- Motion picture -- 1945 -- Paramount, RKO, Universal (Box 345, Folder 1)
    - Strikes -- Motion picture -- 1945 -- Warner Bros. (Box 345, Folder 2-4)
    - Strikes -- Motion picture -- 1946 -- General Views, Columbia (Box 345, Folder 6)
    - Strikes -- Motion picture -- 1946 -- MGM, Republic, Technicolor (Box 345, Folder 7)
    - Strikes -- Motion picture -- 1946 -- Various Studios (Box 345, Folder 5)
    - Strikes -- Motion picture -- 1946 -- Warner Bros. (Box 345, Folder 8)
    - Strikes -- Newspapers (Box 345, Folder 10)
    - Strikes -- Oil workers (Box 345, Folder 9)
    - Strikes -- Railroad (Box 345, Folder 11)
    - Strikes -- Steel (Box 345, Folder 12)
    - Strikes -- Stock Exchange (Box 346, Folder 1)
    - Strikes -- Students (Box 346, Folder 2)
    - Strikes -- Teachers (Box 346, Folder 3)
    - Strikes -- Teamsters (Box 346, Folder 4)
    - Strikes -- Telephone (Box 346, Folder 5-7)
    - Strikes -- Transportation (Box 346, Folder 8)
    - Strikes -- Univis Lens Company (Box 346, Folder 9)
    - Su -- Miscellaneous (Box 336, Folder 11)
    - Submarines (Box 342, Folder 8)
    - Sugar (Box 342, Folder 9)
    - Surgery (Box 334, Folder 2)
    - Sv-sz (Box 336, Folder 12)
    - Swimming (Box 341, Folder 11)
    - Switzerland (Box 334, Folder 3)
    - Taa-Taz (Box 347, Folder 1)
    - Tea-Tel (Box 347, Folder 2)
    - Television (Box 347, Folder 3)
    - Tem-Tez (Box 347, Folder 4)
    - Tennis (Box 347, Folder 5)
    - Th-Tiz (Box 347, Folder 6)
    - Thanksgiving (Box 347, Folder 7-8)
    - Tidal Wave (Box 347, Folder 9-11)
    - Toa-Tow (Box 347, Folder 12)
    - Torpedoes (Box 347, Folder 13)
    - Toy-Toz (Box 347, Folder 14)
    - Tra-Trz (Box 347, Folder 15)
    - Train -- Freedom (Box 348, Folder 1)
    - Train -- Friendship (Box 348, Folder 2)
    - Trampolines -- Sudden Craze for Sport in Los Angeles 1960 (Box 348, Folder 3)
    - Transjordan (Box 348, Folder 4)
    - Treasure (Box 348, Folder 5)
    - Treaties -- Atlantic Pact (Box 348, Folder 6)
    - Treaties -- Japan peace (Box 348, Folder 7)
    - Trieste (Box 348, Folder 8)
    - Triplets and Twins (Box 348, Folder 9)
    - Tua-Tz (Box 348, Folder 10)
    - Turkeys (Box 348, Folder 11-12)
  - U-V
    - U.S. -- Alaska (Box 351, Folder 3)
    - U.S. -- Alaska -- Special pictures (Box 351, Folder 4)
    - U.S. -- Cemeteries (Box 351, Folder 5)
    - U.S. -- Miscellaneous (Box 351, Folder 2)
    - U.S. -- Miscellaneous (Box 355, Folder 1-6)
    - U.S. -- O.P.A. (Box 357, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Army (Box 357, Folder 1-7)
    - U.S. Army -- Academies -- West Point (Box 352, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Army -- Armored Division (Box 352, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Army -- Camps, Bases, Forts (Box 352, Folder 7)
    - U.S. Army -- Cavalry (Box 352, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Army -- Demobilization (Box 352, Folder 9)
    - U.S. Army -- Engineers (Box 352, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Army -- Families (Box 352, Folder 11)
    - U.S. Army -- Fortieth Division (Box 354, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Army -- Guns (Box 354, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Army -- In Africa, Australia, Belgium, England, Germany, Italy, Iwo Jima, Japan, Mexico, New Guinea, and Sicily (Box 354, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Army -- In Alaska (Box 354, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Army -- In France (Box 354, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Army -- In Iceland (Box 354, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Army -- In India (Box 354, Folder 7)
    - U.S. Army -- In Philippines (Box 354, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Army -- Infantry (Box 354, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Army -- Maneuvers (Box 354, Folder 9)
    - U.S. Army -- Medical -- Includes Hospitals, Doctors, etc. (Box 353, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Army -- Miscellaneous -- Envelope II (Box 352, Folder 1-4)
    - U.S. Army -- National Guard (Box 353, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Army -- Nurses (Box 353, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Army -- Recreation (Box 353, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Army -- Redeployment (Box 353, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Army -- Religion, Chaplains, etc. (Box 353, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Army -- Ski and Paratroopers (Box 353, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Army -- Supplies (Box 353, Folder 7)
    - U.S. Army -- Tanks -- Regular and Amphibious (Box 353, Folder 9)
    - U.S. Army -- Training (Box 353, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Army -- Transports (Box 353, Folder 11)
    - U.S. Army -- W.A.C.s (Box 353, Folder 12)
    - U.S. Coast Guard (Box 356, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Congress -- From 1955 (Box 351, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Congress -- Includes Senate Committees, etc. (Box 351, Folder 7)
    - U.S. Congress -- Shooting by Puerto Ricans Monday, March 1, 1954, 5 injured (Box 351, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Constitution (Box 351, Folder 9)
    - U.S. Defense (Box 351, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Marines -- 1938-1947 (Box 356, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Marines -- 1948 (Box 356, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Marines -- 1949 (Box 356, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Marines -- 1950 (Box 360, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Marines -- 1951-1952 (Box 356, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Marines -- 1955 (Box 356, Folder 7)
    - U.S. Marines -- Devil Pups -- 1955 (Box 356, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Marines -- First Division (Box 356, Folder 9)
    - U.S. Marines -- Miscellaneous (Box 356, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Merchant Marine and Maritime Commission (Box 357, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Navy -- Academy -- Annapolis, Maryland -- Miscellaneous (Box 358, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Navy -- Aircraft Carriers (Box 358, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Navy -- Bases -- Miscellaneous (Box 358, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Navy -- Burials at Sea (Box 358, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Navy -- Fleet (Box 358, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Navy -- Frogmen -- Miscellaneous (Box 358, Folder 7)
    - U.S. Navy -- Hospitals -- Ashore and Ship (Box 358, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Navy -- Korea (Box 358, Folder 9)
    - U.S. Navy -- Miscellaneous (Box 358, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Navy -- Ships Unidentified by Name (Box 358, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Navy -- Submarines (Box 358, Folder 11)
    - U.S. Navy -- Torpedo boats (Box 358, Folder 12)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. -- Miscellaneous (Box 359, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. A (Box 359, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Alabama -- Battleship (Box 359, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Enterprise -- Carrier (Box 360, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. F.D. Roosevelt -- Carrier (Box 361, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Franklin -- Carrier (Box 360, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Hornet -- Carrier (Box 359, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Independence (Box 359, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Indiana -- Battleship (Box 359, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Iowa (Box 359, Folder 7)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. J-K (Box 359, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Kearsarge (Box 359, Folder 9)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. L (Box 359, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Laffey (Box 359, Folder 11)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Lexington -- Carrier (Box 360, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. M (Box 359, Folder 12)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Midway -- Carrier (Box 359, Folder 13)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Milwauke (Box 359, Folder 14)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Missouri -- Battleship (Box 359, Folder 15)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. N (Box 359, Folder 16)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Nautilus -- Atomic Submarine (Box 359, Folder 17)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Nevada -- Battleship (Box 359, Folder 18)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. New Jersey (Box 359, Folder 19)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. New York (Box 359, Folder 20)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. O-Q (Box 359, Folder 21)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Pasadena (Box 359, Folder 22)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Pittsburgh -- Cruiser (Box 360, Folder 14)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Saratoga -- Carrier (Box 361, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Solar (Box 361, Folder 9)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Wasp -- Carrier (Box 361, Folder 14)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Wisconsin -- Battleship (Box 361, Folder 16)
    - U.S. Navy -- U.S.S. Yorkstown -- Carrier (Box 361, Folder 17)
    - U.S. Navy -- W.A.V.E.S. (Box 358, Folder 13)
    - U.S. New York City (Box 357, Folder 9)
    - U.S. Philippines (Box 357, Folder 11)
    - U.S. Presidential inauguration -- 1961 (Box 357, Folder 12)
    - U.S. War Dead (Box 357, Folder 13)
    - U.S. Washington, D.C. (Box 357, Folder 14)
    - U.S.S. B (Box 358, Folder 14)
    - U.S.S. Benevolence (Box 358, Folder 15)
    - U.S.S. Boxer (Box 358, Folder 16)
    - U.S.S. Bremerton (Box 356, Folder 10)
    - U.S.S. C (Box 360, Folder 2)
    - U.S.S. Consolation (Box 360, Folder 3)
    - U.S.S. D (Box 360, Folder 4)
    - U.S.S. E-G (Box 360, Folder 5)
    - U.S.S. Essex (Box 360, Folder 7)
    - U.S.S. H-I (Box 360, Folder 9)
    - U.S.S. Leyte (Box 360, Folder 11)
    - U.S.S. Los Angeles (Box 360, Folder 12)
    - U.S.S. Pennsylvania (Box 361, Folder 2)
    - U.S.S. Philippine Sea (Box 360, Folder 13)
    - U.S.S. Princeton (Box 261, Folder 3)
    - U.S.S. R (Box 361, Folder 4)
    - U.S.S. S (Box 361, Folder 5)
    - U.S.S. Saipan (Box 361, Folder 6)
    - U.S.S. Salt Lake City (Box 361, Folder 7)
    - U.S.S. T-V (Box 361, Folder 10)
    - U.S.S. Toledo (Box 361, Folder 11)
    - U.S.S. Valley Forge (Box 361, Folder 12)
    - U.S.S. W-Z (Box 361, Folder 13)
    - U.S.S. Williamsburg (Box 361, Folder 15)
    - United Nations -- 1950 (Box 349, Folder 5)
    - United Nations -- April-May 1946 (Box 349, Folder 3)
    - United Nations -- January-March 1946 (Box 349, Folder 2)
    - United Nations -- July 1946-1948 (Box 349, Folder 4)
    - United Nations Organization -- 1944-1945 (Box 349, Folder 1)
    - Universities -- Miscellaneous -- In and Around Los Angeles (Box 350, Folder 1-6)
    - Universities -- Miscellaneous -- Outside Los Angeles area (Box 350, Folder 7-10)
    - Universities -- UCLA (Box 350, Folder 11)
    - Ur-Urz (Box 348, Folder 13)
    - Uranium -- Mining (Box 351, Folder 1)
    - Va-Vd (Box 362, Folder 1)
    - Vatican City (Box 362, Folder 2)
    - Vaults (Box 362, Folder 3)
    - Ve-Vz (Box 362, Folder 4)
    - Venezuela (Box 362, Folder 5)
    - Veterans -- World War II, Korea (Box 362, Folder 6)
    - Vivisection (Box 362, Folder 7-9)
    - Volcano (Box 362, Folder 10)
    - Volleyball (Box 362, Folder 11)
    - Voting (Box 362, Folder 12)
  - W, X, Y, Z
    - W -- Miscellaneous (Box 363, Folder 1- 4)
    - War Workers (Box 363, Folder 5)
    - Water (Box 363, Folder 6)
    - Water Polo and Skiing (Box 363, Folder 7)
    - Weather -- Hurricane -- "Carla" (Box 363, Folder 8)
    - Weddings (Box 363, Folder 9)
    - Wheat (Box 363, Folder 10)
    - World War II -- Atrocities (Box 363, Folder 11)
    - Wrestling (Box 363, Folder 12)
    - Weather -- Miscellaneous (Box 364, Folder 1-9)
    - Weather -- Cold Blizzards -- Ice, Snow (Box 365, Folder 1)
    - Weather -- Hurricane (Box 365, Folder 2)
    - Weather -- Hurricane -- Donna (Box 365, Folder 3)
    - Weather -- Hurricane -- Europe --1953 (Box 365, Folder 4)
    - Weather -- Smog -- 1954- (Box 365, Folder 5)
    - Weather -- Rain -- Local -- Winter 1952-1954 (Box 366, Folder 1)
    - Weather -- Smog -- 1953 and Prior (Box 366, Folder 2)
    - Weather -- Snow (Box 366, Folder 3-5)
    - Weather -- Snow -- 1955- (Box 366, Folder 6-9)
    - Weather -- Storms (Box 366, Folder 10)
    - Weather -- Local (Box 367, Folder 1-6)
    - Weather -- Tornadoes -- Miscellaneous (Box 367, Folder 7-11)
    - X -- Miscellaneous (Box 368, Folder 1)
    - Y -- Miscellaneous (Box 368, Folder 2)
    - Yachts (Box 368, Folder 3)
    - Youth and Youth Movements (Box 368, Folder 4)
    - Yugoslavia -- U.S. (Box 368, Folder 5)
    - Z -- Miscellaneous (Box 368, Folder 6)